[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "San Marino, Denmark and Norway are among the countries with most _____  per capita.", "correct_answer": "Personal computers", "incorrect_answers": ["Television sets", "Credit cards", "Cell phones"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This stern lady from the movie The Wizard of Oz is Dorothys neighbour, who threatens to have her dog Toto put to sleep.", "correct_answer": "Miss Almira Gulch", "incorrect_answers": ["Miss Fanny Green", "Miss Daisy Green", "Miss Alvina Gray"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these female singers appeared in the 2006 film Eragon?", "correct_answer": "Joss Stone", "incorrect_answers": ["Fergie", "Macy Gray", "Shakira"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This snack food company, founded in 1906, is famous for its peanuts and the Mr. Peanut icon.", "correct_answer": "Planters", "incorrect_answers": ["Skippy", "Diamond Foods", "Con-Agra Foods"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who wrote the book The Color Purple that was adapted into a Broadway play?", "correct_answer": "Alice Walker", "incorrect_answers": ["Betty Pierce", "C.S Lewis", "Anne Rice"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The new food products in Soylent Green are called Soylent Yellow, Red, and Green. The term soylent comes from two foods. One is soy bean. What is the other?", "correct_answer": "Lentils", "incorrect_answers": ["Lettuce", "Lean meat", "Lean chicken"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who plays Big Worm in the film Friday?", "correct_answer": "Faizon Love", "incorrect_answers": ["J. Hart", "Bizarre", "Terrence Howard"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What historical drama, set during Christmas 1183, stars Peter OToole as King Henry II and Katharine Hepburn as Queen Eleanor?", "correct_answer": "The Lion in Winter", "incorrect_answers": ["Lion of the Desert", "The Young Lions", "The Wind and the Lion"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What type of hairstyle is the so-called Fofa?", "correct_answer": "A hairstyle for balding men", "incorrect_answers": ["A hairdo with sideburns", "A frizzy perm", "A tight bun"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What computational device was invented in 1617?", "correct_answer": "Napiers bones", "incorrect_answers": ["Abacus", "Jacquards Loom", "Analytical engine"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What top grossing movie of 1998 features the daughter of Aerosmiths frontman in the role of Grace Stamper?", "correct_answer": "Armageddon", "incorrect_answers": ["Mulan", "Shakespeare in Love", "The Lord of the Rings: The Fellowship of the Ring"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The number of countries that sell  Barbie dolls.", "correct_answer": "140", "incorrect_answers": ["50", "400", "230"]}]